<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Academic Competitions on Ricardo Chin</title><link>https://xsleaks.dev/docs/competitions/</link><description>Recent content in Academic Competitions on Ricardo Chin</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>ricardo.chin@tecnico.ulisboa.pt (Ricardo Chin)</managingEditor><webMaster>ricardo.chin@tecnico.ulisboa.pt (Ricardo Chin)</webMaster><atom:link href="https://xsleaks.dev/docs/competitions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Formula Student Lisbon</title><link>https://xsleaks.dev/docs/competitions/fst/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>ricardo.chin@tecnico.ulisboa.pt (Ricardo Chin)</author><guid>https://xsleaks.dev/docs/competitions/fst/</guid><description>FST 010e | Suspension # warning
Disclaimer: Only partial information is divulged here - mainly for car transmission design, gear fabrication and lubrication. It follows a similar process to the one implemented at Car Transmission Design, but for epicyclical gear trains. 1 Background # During Formula Student (FS) competitions, students are tasked with creating, testing, and refining a race car adhering to specific guidelines outlined by Formula Student Germany (FSG) and Formula Society of Automotive Engineers (FSAE).</description></item><item><title>ThermoCup</title><link>https://xsleaks.dev/docs/competitions/thermocup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>ricardo.chin@tecnico.ulisboa.pt (Ricardo Chin)</author><guid>https://xsleaks.dev/docs/competitions/thermocup/</guid><description>ThermoCup # 1 What is the ThermoCup? # ThermoCup is a unique competition introduced initially at the Technical University of Lisbon during the MecanIST conferences in early 2016. Its primary objective is to challenge participants to conceive, design, and construct a steam boat. The competition covers a comprehensive spectrum of engineering aspects, incorporating various stages of the project lifecycle, from the initial conceptualization and design phase to the practical implementation, prototyping, and subsequent optimization processes.</description></item></channel></rss>